celeb porn spleen
You're still alive.
Five minutes to go.
We have to hurry. This way. Uh-huh!
I'm not going to be a little bit of
a world. I'm a little bit of a world.
I'm gonna be a
little bit
of a world.
I'll see
you
next time.
Oh, oh, oh,
Mutsu daake no Sugou wo So no
Daddy Mutsi haana te Atai naumide le
Oh aata Konno siymi chi
wo City soto Takishimete
no oto ni savaru yoongi
These guys is death gut.
Here we are.
This is where we have to
sign up for the tourney.
It's a typical run-of-the-mill
touch panel interface.
Think you can handle it
or you want some help?
No, I can figure it out. Cool.
I'm going to be over at the next
terminal, so if you get stuck, holler.
Okay, thanks a lot.
Huh?
Oh, we're supposed to
enter our real-life info?
You done yet?
Yes, I'm all done.
Thank you so much for all your help today.
Sorry for all the trouble.
No worries.
That crazy ride on the buggy
more than made up for it.
Anyway, which block did you
end up with for the prelims?
Um, F, I guess.
F-37.
Oh, really?
I'm an F-2, number 12.
That's kind of a cool coincidence, huh?
When did we meet, though?
Oh, good.
We're not going to meet
up again until the finals.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Why is that good?
If a player makes it to the
final bracket in the prelims,
it won't matter if they lose.
They'll automatically
advance to the Battle Royale.
That means we both have a shot at
advancing to the Battle Royale,
as long as we make it
to the last bracket. Oh.
But if we do meet in the final bracket
of the prelims, I'll be playing to win.
Oh.
I get it. All right.
If we both make it, no holding back.
Wow, I'm impressed.
The Japanese translation on
these terminals is pretty good.
The official site was English only.
Well, Zaskar, the company that developed
and runs the game, is American.
They probably have some Japanese
staff to run Japan's server.
Oh, and get this.
I don't know if you knew,
but GDO operates in a legal
gray zone here and in the U .S.
Because of its cash
conversion system, right?
You won't find anything on the company's
homepage except the most basic information.
And as for managing your
character or accessing
your e-money account to
convert what you earn,
any and all game-related procedures
have to be done in the game.
It's amazing.
Shady but amazing.
It is.
The game's practically
independent of the real world.
Maybe that's why the
person I am in here and
the real me feel like
two different people.
Sorry, I don't know why I went there.
We should start heading
over to the prelim area now.
You ready to go?
Sure. That way.
It's in the basement.
Something wrong huh?
No, nothing good.
Let's go to the waiting room first!
You're gonna need some privacy to
change into your new combat suit. Right?
I swear, what a bunch of dumbasses. Huh?
Who do you mean?
Those tough-looking guys outside?
Yeah, them.
It's a half hour before the match,
and they're out there showing
off their main weapons.
It's like they're asking you to
come up with a countermeasure.
Oh, yeah.
That is silly.
Piece of advice,
don't equip your photon sword in 5-7
until just before your match starts.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Huh?
Don't just stand there.
Hurry up and get changed already.
Uh, yes.
I mean, I can't.
I mean, I can't change now.
I, I mean, I'm sorry. Why?
I haven't introduced myself.
This is who I really am.
Okay.
Kirito. Huh.
Well, it's an interesting
name, I'll give you that.
Wait!
Male?!
But...
You're a...
You're kidding!
No way!
You're a guy with that avatar?!
You Why you
Stop following me.
But I'm not sure what I'm
supposed to do after this.
Stop following me.
Okay, but I don't know anyone else here.
But, but I...
I'll explain it, but just
the bare minimum, that's it.
After that, you and me are enemies.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, well, just so we're clear,
this doesn't mean I forgive you.
You see that clock up there?
When it hits zero, everyone here will be
automatically transferred to a battlefield,
along with whoever their
first-round opponent's gonna be.
You with me so far?
Yeah.
The field's a square.
Each side's a kilometer.
The weather, terrain, and time
are all randomly generated.
Your opponent's placed
500 meters away from you.
Whoever wins the match
gets transferred back here.
The losers transfer to
the first floor hall.
And you don't get penalized
for losing a match.
There are 64 people in Block F, so
five wins will take you to the final?
and you'll be eligible
for the Battle Royale.
That's it.
No more questions.
I'm done helping you.
I think I got the gist of it.
And thanks again.
You better reach the finals.
Because even after everything
I taught you today,
there's one thing left for you to learn.
Yeah, what?
The taste of the bullet that beats you.
I'll look forward to it.
What about you, though?
You think you'll make it to the finals?
I'll retire if I get
knocked out of the prelims.
But I won't.
Not this time.
This time, I'll kill
all the strong players.
Since this is the last time we'll be
chatting like this, you should know my name.
There it is.
The name of the person
who's gonna beat you.
Xenon.
I'm Kirito. Nice to meet you.
Hey about time you showed
up I couldn't find you
anywhere and I was worried
you weren't gonna make it.
Sorry about that Spiegel I totally lost
track of time thanks to an unexpected chore.
Hey hang on you said you weren't
competing did you change your mind?
Well even though I know how much it bugs
you I thought I'd sort of cheer you on from
the sidelines I already
picked out a spot in
in front of the jumbo
screen and everything.
What was that unexpected
chore you were talking about?
Oh, nothing.
I was just giving this
person a sort of orientation.
That'd be me.
Hi, how's it going?
Oh, hi, it's nice to meet you.
So are you a friend of Sinon's?
Hate to break it to you, but she's a dude.
Yeah, my name's Kirito. I'm a dude.
A guy?
Why?
Then does that mean
he's, uh, that you're...
Not even.
Hey, Sinon, thanks for
showing me a good time.
It was a great first date.
What the hell are you saying?
It wasn't a good time,
and it was not a date.
It was a mistake, so forget my
name and forget we ever met.
Oh, come on.
Don't be so heartless.
Heartless, my ass.
I don't even know you.
But we spent the whole day
together picking out all my gear.
Yeah, but only because you...
Thank you for your patience, players.
I hope you're ready.
because the third Bullet of Bullets
preliminary tournament is about to begin.
When the countdown clock reaches zero,
all competing players will
be automatically transported?
to their respective
first-round field maps.
Good luck to you all.
You better make it to the finals,
because I'm looking forward
to blowing your head off.
I accept the invitation, but
don't keep me waiting too long.
Why you...
Maybe I went a little too far there.
This time, I'll kill
all the strong players.
Is that possible?
Could she be Death Gun?
I saw two sides of her, but
which is the real Sinon?
I won't find out standing
here, thinking about it.
But if we cross swords, I mean, traded
shots, I'm sure I'll find the answer.
Let's go.
I can't dodge all those bullets.
At this rate, I'll never
get closer to them.
Maybe if I could use my sword to
deflect the bullets, I could get closer.
They're flying too damn fast, though.
There's no way I can predict
the trajectory of each bullet.
No, I can do this.
The bullet lines tell me exactly
what path the bullets are traveling.
I don't know.
No!
Holy crap!
Just a little further!
Ah, damn it.
I can't believe I have to
do this four more times.
I wonder where Xenon is.
Are you the real deal?
The real deal?
What do you mean by that?
Who are you?
I saw your match.
You took him out with
a sword. Yeah? So what?
It's not against the rules, is it?
I'll ask you again.
Are you the real deal?
Wait, does he know me?
No way, we have met before.
We've been face to face like this,
but where, where do I know him from?
With that name and your sword skills,
are you the real deal or what?
If he knows me?
I should know him.
That's it.
He's an SAO survivor.
Who is he?
And where did we meet? An SAO.
Let's go.
Ah!
More stronger, more stronger!
I want to say that I want to!
I want to be the saddest!
I've never been
to
the
past.
I've never been to the past.
I'm not going to look at all the pain!
I'm not going to die all
alone! I'm not going to die!
I'm not going to die!
I'm not going
to
die!
So strong, I want to say that
I want to go to the dark.
I can't be able to say that I can't.
Next time, Showdown in the Wilderness.